<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tips with Tim</title>
    <description>Tim Peirce, a top Real Estate Agent in Hilton Head Island, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 14:43:52 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 14:43:52 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s the Best CRM?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FHUqb6Jdacc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;The popular CRMs available to agents and how to get organized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the best CRM to use in the real estate business, and how do you organize it? There’s almost no limit to the number of CRMs that you can choose from, and it can be overwhelming for agents. The most important thing to remember is that &lt;strong&gt;the best CRM is the one that you will use&lt;/strong&gt;. On my team, we use Follow-Up Boss, but there are other CRMs like Hubspot, Command, Commissions Inc., and Boomtown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you get a CRM set up, organize it quickly. I sort buyers and sellers into three different categories: A, B, and C. Category A are those likely to buy or sell in the next 30 days, B is within the next 30 to 90 days, and C is 90 days to six months. Build a plan around your CRM. There should be a call cadence and marketing plan for how you get in touch with these people. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you need help organizing your CRM or have any other questions, visit my website, and don’t hesitate to reach out by phone or email to book a 15-minute call with me. I’d be happy to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-the-best-crm.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/whats-the-best-crm.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Building a Database From Scratch</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/SWKEuTCKBug?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;Your database is one of your most valuable assets and useful tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you start building your database if you’re a brand-new agent or if you’re new to a given market?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team is really good at getting brand new agents off the ground quickly and helping them build their databases. One of the exercises that we do is called “The Places That You Go.” We give them a worksheet with nine bubbles and five lines under each bubble. Think about all the different places you go in your week and list five people that you’ve engaged with there that you know could potentially refer you or provide other value. This is how you start building your database.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then just start reaching out to them with regularity. It shouldn’t always be you asking them for business. You should also be offering something of value. Maybe they need a referral for a plumber or a handyman. &lt;strong&gt;Offering value and building relationships will build your database.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or want to schedule a call to talk about building your database, don’t hesitate to reach out to us via email or our website. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 23:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/building-a-database-from-scratch.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/building-a-database-from-scratch.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <category>Stories</category>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Agent Testimonial | Jamie Franklin</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/1_xfO9D0t38?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 10:40:15 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/agent-testimonial-jamie-franklin.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/agent-testimonial-jamie-franklin.html</guid>
        
        <category>Stories</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Agent Q&amp;A: How Do You Tackle Buyer’s Remorse?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z8h3_b17HQ8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;Here’s how to help your clients who are dealing with buyer’s remorse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the top agents in the Peirce Group came to me the other day, telling me that he had a buyer who was freaking out about an inspection and wanted out of the deal. How did we fix it? Today I’ll share how we handled this precarious situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The question was whether the buyer wanted to back out because of the inspection or because they had buyer’s remorse.&lt;/strong&gt; Later, we learned that it was in fact buyer’s remorse. We learned something very tactical from this experience: You need to talk about buyer’s remorse with your clients right after they go under contract.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Remind them that you’re here for them throughout the process.%20http://localhost:4000/agent-qa-how-do-you-tackle-buyers-remorse.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Remind them that you’re here for them throughout the process.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I often say something to the effect of, “Now that you’ve signed this contract, you might go home and lose sleep over it. Most people do! It’s a very simple thing called buyer’s remorse, and it’s usually the worst on the second and third days after going under contract.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make sure to add that your clients should come to you when they’re having these feelings.&lt;/strong&gt; Remind them that you’re here for them throughout the process, and set expectations with them upfront so that you can help them navigate the emotional aspects of the process as well. There’s nothing more impactful than telling a story about how you’ve had buyer’s remorse yourself at some point; show them that you know how they feel and that you know to move forward through it. In the end, don’t let one excuse allow a contract to go under. Most of the time, it’s not actually because of the excuse they give you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or need help in navigating your own client’s buyer’s remorse, don’t hesitate to reach out to me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/agent-qa-how-do-you-tackle-buyers-remorse.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/agent-qa-how-do-you-tackle-buyers-remorse.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zillow Is No Longer Purchasing Properties</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BO5Fv0T_XXI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;Here’s why Zillow has stopped buying homes for the foreseeable future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t seen the recent headlines, there was big news for a real estate tech giant recently. &lt;strong&gt;Zillow announced to the world that it is shuttering its iBuying business, Zillow Offers.&lt;/strong&gt; This comes after the news that they are writing down $304 million in Q3 and laying off 2,000 employees. Wall Street didn’t like this news much, and the stock tumbled 18%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zillow was committed to buying nearly 9,680 homes based solely on their algorithm, but they realized that a significant portion of the homes they purchased are now worth less than what they paid for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Computer-based models are always riddled with flaws.%20http://localhost:4000/zillow-is-no-longer-purchasing-properties-1.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Computer-based models are always riddled with flaws.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15 years ago, Zillow invented their computer-based valuation system, also known as the Zestimate. It is their claim to fame and ultimately what drew consumers to their site. Yet, after billions invested and continued refinement in the Zestimate, it’s still proving to be unreliable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does this all mean? Is there a crash coming? &lt;strong&gt;Quite the opposite!&lt;/strong&gt; Research has continually shown that these computer-based models are riddled with flaws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem is that the big tech and iBuying companies are putting too much faith in machines to do what humans can do better. Just because something can be automated doesn’t mean that it should be. The bottom line is that the best person to help you price your home remains a seasoned real estate professional, not artificial intelligence!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have questions for me about your home’s value or anything else related to real estate, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/zillow-is-no-longer-purchasing-properties-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/zillow-is-no-longer-purchasing-properties-1.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate News</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hear what our agents are saying!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/oaSCkfv9uiQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch this short video to hear what our agents have to say about working with The Peirce Group.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 10:41:12 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/hear-what-our-agents-are-saying.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/hear-what-our-agents-are-saying.html</guid>
        
        <category>Stories</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
